export const QuizzData = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "What is the basic accounting equation?",
      choices: [
        "Assets = Liabilities + Equity",
        "Revenue - Expenses = Profit",
        "Debits = Credits",
        "Income = Expenditure",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Assets = Liabilities + Equity",
    },
    {
      question: "Which accounting principle matches expenses to revenues?",
      choices: [
        "Matching Principle",
        "Revenue Recognition Principle",
        "Conservatism Principle",
        "Materiality Principle",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Matching Principle",
    },
    {
      question: "Which financial statement shows a company's profitability?",
      choices: [
        "Income Statement",
        "Balance Sheet",
        "Statement of Cash Flows",
        "Statement of Retained Earnings",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Income Statement",
    },
    {
      question: "What does GAAP stand for in accounting?",
      choices: [
        "Generally Accepted Accounting Principles",
        "General Accounting Assessment Procedures",
        "Global Accounting Analysis Process",
        "Governmental Accounting Applications and Procedures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Generally Accepted Accounting Principles",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which accounting method records revenues and expenses when they are incurred, regardless of when cash is exchanged?",
      choices: [
        "Cash basis accounting",
        "Accrual basis accounting",
        "Double-entry accounting",
        "Cost accounting",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Accrual basis accounting",
    },
    {
      question: "What is depreciation in accounting?",
      choices: [
        "An increase in asset value",
        "A decrease in liability",
        "The allocation of cost of an asset over its useful life",
        "An increase in shareholder equity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "The allocation of cost of an asset over its useful life",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which financial ratio measures a company's ability to pay short-term obligations with its most liquid assets?",
      choices: [
        "Current ratio",
        "Quick ratio",
        "Debt-to-equity ratio",
        "Return on investment",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Quick ratio",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'trial balance' in accounting?",
      choices: [
        "To verify the accuracy of the ledger accounts",
        "To prepare financial statements",
        "To calculate depreciation",
        "To record adjusting entries",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "To verify the accuracy of the ledger accounts",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which financial statement reports the changes in equity over a period?",
      choices: [
        "Income Statement",
        "Balance Sheet",
        "Statement of Changes in Equity",
        "Cash Flow Statement",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Statement of Changes in Equity",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of an audit in accounting?",
      choices: [
        "To prepare tax returns",
        "To verify the accuracy of financial statements",
        "To predict future financial performance",
        "To calculate depreciation",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "To verify the accuracy of financial statements",
    },
  ],
};

export const resultInitalState = {
  score: 0,
  correctAnswers: 0,
  wrongAnswers: 0,
};
